<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Astrology</string>
    <string name="tab">\u0009</string>
    <string name="textdata"> wefbwbibivbifbviberuvbwbvhjfbvhbadfhvblabfvhabfjhvbasfhvbhadfbvjhabfvhabslfjhvbasjfhbvlajhbfvjahbdfjhvbajsdvjhsbadhvbalkfbvjsdbfvjhbadjfhvbakdfvblahdbfvljhbvlhjabdfhvbakfdbvahbdfvkjbadkfhvbadkhfvbkadbfvkabkfvbadkfvbakdbfvkahdbfvkhabkdfhbvkashbfvkjasnvkjbajshfvbjabfvasbvjhbsvjhbasvjhbasjhvbaskbvjhbasvhjbadfhcbads</string>
    <string name="zodiac">sign</string>
    <string name="name_aries">Aries</string>
    <string name="name_taurus">Taurus</string>
    <string name="name_gemini">Gemini</string>
    <string name="name_cancer">Cancer</string>
    <string name="name_leo">Leo</string>
    <string name="name_virgo">Virgo</string>
    <string name="name_libra">Libra</string>
    <string name="name_scorpio">Scorpio</string>
    <string name="name_sagittarius">Sagittarius</string>
    <string name="name_Capricorn">Capricorn</string>
    <string name="name_aquarius">Aquarius</string>
    <string name="name_pisces">Pisces</string>
    <string name="date_aries">March 21 - April 19</string>
    <string name="date_taurus">April 20 - May 20</string>
    <string name="date_gemini">May 21 - June 20</string>
    <string name="date_cancer">June 21 - July 22</string>
    <string name="date_leo">July 23 - August 22</string>
    <string name="date_virgo">August 23 - September 22</string>
    <string name="date_libra">September 23 - October 22</string>
    <string name="date_scorpio">October 23 - November 22 </string>
    <string name="date_sagittarius">November 22 - December 21</string>
    <string name="date_Capricorn">December 22 - January 19</string>
    <string name="date_aquarius">January 20 - February 18</string>
    <string name="date_pisces">February 18 – March 20</string>
    <string name="about_aries">Aries is the first astrological sign in the zodiac, spanning the first 30 degrees of celestial longitude. Under the tropical zodiac, the Sun transits this sign mostly from March 21 to April 20 each year. This time duration is exactly the first month of Solar Hejri calendar. The symbol of the ram is based on the Chrysomallus, the flying ram that provided the Golden Fleece.</string>
    <string name="about_taurus">Taurus is the second astrological sign in the present zodiac. It spans the 30–60th degree of the zodiac. The Sun is in the sign of Taurus from about April 20 until about May 21. People born between these dates, depending on which system of astrology they subscribe to, may be called Taureans.</string>
    <string name="about_gemini">Gemini is the third astrological sign in the zodiac, originating from the constellation of Gemini. Under the tropical zodiac, the sun transits this sign between May 21 and June 21. Gemini is represented by The Twins Castor and Pollux. The symbol of the twins is based on the Dioscuri, two mortals that were granted shared godhood after death.</string>
    <string name="about_cancer">Cancer is the fourth astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating from the constellation of Cancer. It spans the 90° to 120° of the zodiac, between 90° and 120° of celestial longitude. Under the tropical zodiac, the Sun transits this area on average between June 22 and July 22, and under the sidereal zodiac, the Sun transits this area between approximately July 16 and August 15.</string>
    <string name="about_leo">Leo is the fifth astrological sign of the zodiac, originating from the constellation of Leo. It comes after Cancer and before Virgo. Under the tropical zodiac, the Sun transits this area approximately between July 23 and August 22; the sign spans the 120th to 150th degree of celestial longitude</string>
    <string name="about_virgo">Virgo is the sixth astrological sign in the Zodiac. Virgo is the second-largest constellation. It spans the 150-180th degree of the zodiac. Under the tropical zodiac, the Sun transits this area on average between August 23 and September 22, and under the sidereal zodiac, the sun transits the constellation of Virgo from September 17 to October 17. Individuals born during these dates, depending on which system of astrology they subscribe to, may be called Virgos or Virgoans. The symbol of the maiden is based on Astraea. In Greek mythology, she was the last immortal to abandon Earth at the end of the Silver Age, when the gods fled to Olympus - hence the sign is association with Earth.</string>
    <string name="about_libra">Libra is the seventh astrological sign in the Zodiac. It spans the 180–210th degree of the zodiac, between 180 and 207.25 degree of celestial longitude. Under the tropical zodiac, Sun transits this area on average between September 23 and October 22, and under the sidereal zodiac, the sun currently transits the constellation of Libra from approximately October 16 to November 17. The symbol of the scales is based on the Scales of Justice held by Themis, the Greek personification of divine law and custom. She became the inspiration for modern depictions of Lady Justice. The ruling planet of Libra is Venus. Libra is the only zodiac constellation in the sky represented by an inanimate object. The other eleven signs are represented either as an animal or mythological characters throughout history.</string>
    <string name="about_scorpio">Scorpio is the eighth astrological sign in the Zodiac. It spans the 210–240th degree of the zodiac, between 207.25 and 234.75 degree of celestial longitude. Under the tropical zodiac, the sun transits this area on average from October 23 to November 22, and under the sidereal zodiac, the sun currently transits the constellation of Scorpius from approximately November 16 to December 15. Depending on which zodiac system one uses, an individual born under the influence of Scorpio may be called a Scorpio or a Scorpion.</string>
    <string name="about_sagittarius">Sagittarius is the ninth astrological sign, which is associated with the constellation Sagittarius and spans 240–270th degrees of the zodiac. Under the tropical zodiac, the sun transits this sign between approximately November 23 and December 21. Greek mythology associates Sagittarius with the centaur Chiron, who mentored Achilles, a Greek hero of the Trojan War, in archery.</string>
    <string name="about_Capricorn">Capricorn is the tenth astrological sign in the zodiac, originating from the constellation of Capricornus. It spans the 270–300th degree of the zodiac, corresponding to celestial longitude. Under the tropical zodiac, the sun transits this area from December 22 to January 19 each year, and under the sidereal zodiac, the sun transits the constellation of Capricorn from approximately January 16 to February 16. In astrology, Capricorn is considered an earth sign, negative sign, and one of the four cardinal signs. Capricorn is said to be ruled by the planet Saturn. Its symbol is based on the Sumerians primordial god of wisdom and waters, Enki, with the head and upper body of a goat and the lower body and tail of a fish. Later known as Ea in Akkadian and Babylonian mythology, Enki was the god of intelligence, creation, crafts; magic; water, seawater and lakewater.</string>
    <string name="about_aquarius">Aquarius is the eleventh astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating from the constellation Aquarius. Under the tropical zodiac, the sun is in Aquarius typically between January 21 and February 18, while under the Sidereal Zodiac, the sun is in Aquarius from approximately February 15 to March 14, depending on leap year.</string>
    <string name="about_pisces">Pisces is the twelfth astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating from the Pisces constellation. It spans the 330° to 360° of the zodiac, between 332.75° and 360° of celestial longitude. Under the tropical zodiac the sun transits this area on average between February 19 and March 20, and under the sidereal zodiac, the sun transits this area between approximately March 13 and April 13. The symbol of the fish is derived from the ichthyocentaurs, who aided Aphrodite when she was born from the sea.</string>
</resources>